(Bernadette:)That's the wrong arm
for a heart attack, doofus.
(Howard:)My point is, I'm sure there are
things about me
(Howard:)that would drive you crazy if you had
to deal with them all day long.
(Bernadette:)Like looking me in the eye
and lying to me?
Come on, I just...
(Howard:)Where am I supposed to look
when I lie to you?
(Bernadette:)Find somewhere else
to sleep tonight.
(Howard:)Bernie...
(Sheldon:)If it makes you feel any better,
Amy and I are time.
(Sheldon:)I mean, really good.
(Leonard:)So, boys,
how was the pajama party?
(Leonard:)You guys jump on the bed
and sing into hair brushes?
It wasn't a pajama party.
(Raj:)It was just a couple of bros
hanging out, giggling,
(Raj:)eating cookie dough
and watching Princess Bride.
(Howard:)Please, stop talking.